In love and medicine, malpractice makes perfect
Foreign Body is a comedy film directed by Ronald Neame.
Banerjee stars as Ram Das, a jobless Indian man who, tired of life in Calcutta, steals money from his father
in order to afford a passage to Britain and while there, falls in love with a white woman.
Ram Das, played by Victor Banerjee.
I.Q. Patel, played by Warren Mitchell.
Lady Ammanford, played by Geraldine McEwan.
Prime Minister, played by Denis Quilley.
Susan Partridge, played by Amanda Donohoe.
Norah, played by Eve Ferret.
Foreign Body is a 1986 British romantic comedy film directed by Ronald Neame
and adapted from the 1975 Roderick Mann novel of the same name.
The film stars Victor Banerjee, Warren Mitchell,
Denis Quilley, and Amanda Donohoe.
It was Neame's final film.
The tone is lighthearted.